Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Starlit Bloom=
=ازهار النجوم=
=Episode 13=
=الحلقة 13=
We...
نحن...
What's it?
ما هو؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Just thinking about what you said about eco-friendly materials.
فقط أفكر فيما قلته عن المواد الصديقة للبيئة.
If we want to switch materials for Starry Sea,
إذا أردنا تبديل المواد الخاصة بـ Starry Sea،
why not just use gold?
لماذا لا نستخدم الذهب فقط؟
Why do we need...
لماذا نحتاج...
Hey, Ms. Gu.
مرحباً، السيدة جو.
This is kind of an intimate moment.
هذه لحظة حميمة نوعا ما.
You sure you want to talk about work?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تريد التحدث عن العمل؟
(Ms. Gu?)
(السيدة جو؟)
Fair point.
نقطة عادلة.
If we use existing raw materials,
إذا استخدمنا المواد الخام الموجودة،
we will save costs.
سوف نوفر التكاليف.
(Will I embarrass myself for bringing it up first?)
(هل سأحرج نفسي إذا طرحت هذا الموضوع أولاً؟)
But if mining
ولكن إذا كان التعدين
continues unchecked,
يستمر دون رادع،
what we gain will never make up for what we lose.
ما نكتسبه لن يعوضنا أبدًا عما نخسره.
"What we gain will never make up for what we lose."
"ما نكتسبه لن يعوضنا أبدًا عما نخسره."
Yes.
نعم.
All right, I'll think about it some more.
حسنًا، سأفكر في الأمر أكثر.
♪Frozen memories♪
♪ذكريات مجمدة♪
I'll think with you.
سأفكر معك.
♪Brought up by chance♪
♪نشأت بالصدفة♪
♪Your name struck a chord in my heart♪
♪اسمك أثار صدى في قلبي♪
Ms. Gu.
السيدة جو.
The annual report.
التقرير السنوي.
Oh, right, the annual report.
أوه، صحيح، التقرير السنوي.
Just email it to me.
فقط أرسله لي بالبريد الإلكتروني.
All right. I'll email you.
حسنًا، سأرسل لك بريدًا إلكترونيًا.
Okay...
تمام...
That was too close. Too close.
كان ذلك قريبًا جدًا. قريبًا جدًا.
Did that hurt?
هل كان ذلك مؤلمًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Sorry.
آسف.
Lu Xingchen, have you ever thought about resigning?
لو شينغتشين، هل فكرت يومًا في الاستقالة؟
Hey, Gu Liusu.
مهلا، قو ليوسو.
Could you really let me go?
هل يمكنك حقا أن تسمح لي بالذهاب؟
After all, I'm the personal secretary
بعد كل شيء، أنا السكرتير الشخصي
you worked so hard to train.
لقد عملت بجد للتدريب.
Well, let's get to work then.
حسنًا، فلنبدأ العمل إذن.
Okay.
تمام.
(No.)
(لا.)
(He has to say it first.)
(عليه أن يقول ذلك أولاً.)
(I won't let a little boy pull my strings.)
(لن أسمح لطفل صغير أن يتحكم في خيوطي.)
Where is she?
أين هي؟
Ms. Gu already clocked out.
لقد انتهت السيدة جو من عملها بالفعل.
Gu Liusu!
قو ليوسو!
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Home.
بيت.
Home?
بيت؟
Let's go home.
دعنا نذهب إلى المنزل.
Lu Xingchen.
لو شينغتشن.
What are we?
ما نحن؟
Whatever you think we are,
مهما كنت تعتقد أننا،
that's what we are.
هذا ما نحن عليه.
We seem to get along, sure.
يبدو أننا نتفق، بالتأكيد.
But what are you to me, really?
ولكن ماذا أنت بالنسبة لي، حقا؟
We're...
كان...
(So you won't make a move, reject me, and take responsibility, huh?)
(لذا لن تقوم بأي خطوة، وترفضني، وتتحمل المسؤولية، أليس كذلك؟)
We've slept together.
لقد نمنا معًا.
♪I'll admit, I didn't love you enough♪
♪سأعترف، أنني لم أحبك بما فيه الكفاية♪
(That's what you think too, right?)
(هذا ما تعتقده أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟)
(After all, what we have isn't something)
(في نهاية المطاف، ما لدينا ليس شيئا)
(to be shown in the open.)
(للعرض في العلن.)
♪Maybe I was just messing around♪
♪ربما كنت أمزح فقط♪
♪After all♪
♪بعد كل شيء♪
♪The character I played was that I didn't love you enough♪
♪الشخصية التي لعبتها هي أنني لم أحبك بما فيه الكفاية♪
If there's nothing else, I'll head back.
إذا لم يكن هناك شيء آخر، سأعود.
♪But that didn't stop me from trying to find you♪
♪ولكن هذا لم يمنعني من محاولة العثور عليك♪
♪I'm trying, trying to forget you♪
♪أحاول، أحاول أن أنساك♪
(So that's how she sees us.)
(وهكذا ترانا).
♪It might look like I don't care that much♪
♪قد يبدو الأمر وكأنني لا أهتم كثيرًا♪
♪When I said it, said it, said I didn't love you enough♪
♪عندما قلتها، قلتها، قلت أنني لم أحبك بما فيه الكفاية♪
(Did I mess up again?)
(هل أخطأت مرة أخرى؟)
♪And you believed me♪
♪وصدقتني♪
♪I've said a bunch of things, some of which made sense♪
♪لقد قلت مجموعة من الأشياء، بعضها كان منطقيًا♪
♪Like how we never loved the same way♪
♪كما أننا لم نحب بنفس الطريقة أبدًا♪
♪I'm not good at saying "I love you"♪
♪أنا لست جيدًا في قول "أنا أحبك"♪
♪But I always carry an umbrella because I know you like the rain♪
♪لكنني أحمل دائمًا مظلة لأنني أعلم أنك تحب المطر♪
(We've slept together.)
(لقد نمنا معًا.)
♪And every rainy day, through all those little things♪
♪وفي كل يوم ممطر، من خلال كل تلك الأشياء الصغيرة♪
♪I've tucked my quiet love inside each one of them♪
♪لقد خبأت حبي الهادئ داخل كل واحد منهم♪
♪Even if it's just a little bit, I keep giving it until it's all gone♪
♪حتى لو كان القليل فقط، سأستمر في العطاء حتى ينتهي كل شيء♪
♪You believed me♪
♪لقد صدقتني♪
♪I'll admit, I didn't love you enough♪
♪سأعترف، أنني لم أحبك بما فيه الكفاية♪
(Did I say too much?)
(هل قلت الكثير؟)
(I didn't even ask what he thought.)
(لم أسأله حتى عما يعتقده.)
♪I never wanted to fall this hard♪
♪لم أرغب أبدًا في السقوط بهذه القوة♪
(But he didn't deny it either.)
(ولكنه لم ينكر ذلك أيضًا).
(Maybe that means he agrees.)
(ربما يعني هذا أنه موافق.)
♪I didn't love you enough♪
♪لم احبك بما فيه الكفاية♪
♪Why are there always stars at night?♪
♪لماذا هناك دائما نجوم في الليل؟♪
♪Why do your eyes always sparkle?♪
♪لماذا تتألق عيناك دائمًا؟♪
♪Why does Coke always need ice?♪
لماذا يحتاج الكوك دائمًا إلى الثلج؟
♪Why do I always stop to listen for your heartbeat?♪
♪لماذا أتوقف دائمًا للاستماع إلى دقات قلبك؟♪
♪Why can't I see it clearly now?♪
♪لماذا لا أستطيع أن أرى ذلك بوضوح الآن؟♪
♪Can't see your silhouette♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية صورتك الظلية♪
♪Can't hear your voice♪
♪لا أستطيع سماع صوتك♪
♪How did we end up like this?♪
♪كيف انتهى بنا الأمر هكذا؟♪
Was I wrong?
هل كنت مخطئا؟
The more I care, the more I want to run.
كلما زاد اهتمامي، كلما زادت رغبتي في الركض.
Keep searching for what's wrong inside you.
استمر في البحث عما هو خطأ بداخلك.
You shouldn't be afraid to show flaws or weaknesses.
لا ينبغي أن تخاف من إظهار العيوب أو نقاط الضعف.
Nothing in this world is perfect anyway.
لا يوجد شيء مثالي في هذا العالم على أية حال.
Your childhood trauma from separation
صدمة طفولتك بسبب الانفصال
has made you afraid
لقد جعلك خائفا
of being abandoned again.
من التخلي عنها مرة أخرى.
When you get used to protecting yourself too much,
عندما تعتاد على حماية نفسك كثيرًا،
you start caring too much,
تبدأ بالاهتمام كثيرًا،
and the more you care, the harder it becomes to say
وكلما زاد اهتمامك، أصبح من الصعب قول ذلك.
"I need you".
"أنا بحاجة إليك".
Maybe you're right.
ربما كنت على حق.
I shouldn't push away the people who care about me.
لا ينبغي لي أن أبتعد عن الأشخاص الذين يهتمون بي.
Mm.
مم.
I have to go, Dr. Yu.
يجب أن أذهب، دكتور يو.
Gu Liusu!
قو ليوسو!
Hi, pretty lady!
مرحباً سيدتي الجميلة!
We meet again!
لقد التقينا مرة أخرى!
I thought about it all night,
لقد فكرت في هذا الأمر طوال الليل،
and I finally figured out what you really want.
وأخيرًا توصلت إلى ما تريده حقًا.
Love
حب
should start with flowers
ينبغي أن تبدأ بالزهور
and a real confession.
واعتراف حقيقي.
So I want to tell you,
لذلك أريد أن أخبرك،
we're not just two people who slept together.
نحن لسنا مجرد شخصين ينامان معًا.
And it didn't start by accident either.
ولم يبدأ الأمر بالصدفة أيضًا.
♪Mayday♪
♪ماي داي♪
I might not have prepared everything perfectly,
ربما لم أقم بإعداد كل شيء بشكل مثالي،
but I want you to remember this day, okay?
لكن أريدك أن تتذكر هذا اليوم، حسنًا؟
Lu Xingchen
لو شينغتشن
likes Gu Liusu.
يحب قو ليوسو.
Lu Xingchen only likes Gu Liusu.
Lu Xingchen يحب Gu Liusu فقط.
Lu Xingchen
لو شينغتشن
likes Gu Liusu more than anyone else
يحب جو ليوسو أكثر من أي شخص آخر
in the whole
في المجمل
wide
واسع
world!
عالم!
(Maybe people who overthink everything)
(ربما الناس الذين يفكرون كثيرا في كل شيء)
(do need someone who loves them with certainty.)
(يحتاجون إلى شخص يحبهم بالتأكيد.)
(I pretend I don't need anyone,)
(أتظاهر بأنني لا أحتاج إلى أحد)
(but deep down I hope someone can see right through me.)
(لكن في أعماقي أتمنى أن يتمكن شخص ما من رؤيتي بوضوح.)
(When he appeared in front of me,)
(حين ظهر أمامي)
(it felt like a soft light)
(شعرت وكأنه ضوء خافت)
(breaking through the dark forest.)
(اختراق الغابة المظلمة.)
(I didn't even think about what lay beyond that light.)
(لم أفكر حتى في ما يكمن وراء هذا الضوء.)
(I just lowered my guard)
(لقد خفضت حذري للتو)
(and stepped out of the forest.)
(وخرج من الغابة.)
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪Maybe we were never meant to be♪
♪ربما لم يكن من المفترض أن نكون معًا♪
I can't get the bear suit off.
لا أستطيع خلع بدلة الدب.
Hold on.
يتمسك.
I'll let some air out of it.
سأسمح لبعض الهواء بالخروج منه.
♪Faded moments gone by♪
♪لحظات باهتة مضت♪
Gu Liusu,
قو ليوسو,
be my girlfriend.
كن صديقتي.
Please?
لو سمحت؟
♪Maybe, just maybe♪
♪ربما، ربما فقط♪
♪If I had never chosen to give up♪
♪لو لم أختر الاستسلام أبدًا♪
♪The dog we raised is still around♪
♪الكلب الذي قمنا بتربيته لا يزال موجودًا♪
♪Despite the setbacks, it still feels like a kind of luck♪
♪على الرغم من النكسات، لا يزال الأمر يبدو وكأنه نوع من الحظ♪
♪Funny♪
♪مضحك♪
♪Isn't it?♪
♪أليس كذلك؟♪
♪Only after losing you did I see your love was worth keeping♪
♪فقط بعد أن فقدتك رأيت أن حبك يستحق الاحتفاظ به♪
You know what?
أتعلم؟
I was just about to come find you too.
لقد كنت على وشك أن آتي للبحث عنك أيضًا.
♪For letting you slip away into the crowd with my own hands♪
♪لأني سمحت لك بالانزلاق إلى الحشد بيدي ♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
(I'm glad I met you,)
(أنا سعيد أنني التقيت بك)
(Lu Xingchen.)
(لو شينغتشن.)
♪At the wrong time, I found the one I loved most♪
♪في الوقت الخطأ، وجدت الشخص الذي أحببته أكثر♪
♪Does that still count as luck?♪
♪هل لا يزال هذا يعتبر حظًا؟♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪Maybe we were never meant to be♪
♪ربما لم يكن من المفترض أن نكون معًا♪
=Starlit Bloom=
=ازهار النجوم=
♪But I can't escape♪
♪لكنني لا أستطيع الهروب♪
♪The memories of you♪
♪ذكرياتك♪
♪The harder I try to forget♪
♪كلما حاولت أن أنسى♪
♪The more you come back to me♪
♪كلما عدت إلي أكثر♪
♪Two hearts once in love collide and shatter into pieces♪
♪قلبان كانا في حالة حب تصادما وتحطما إلى قطع♪
♪How can I piece myself together again?♪
♪كيف يمكنني أن أجمع نفسي مرة أخرى؟♪
♪Funny, isn't it?♪
♪مضحك، أليس كذلك؟♪
♪Only after losing you did I see your love was worth keeping♪
♪فقط بعد أن فقدتك رأيت أن حبك يستحق الاحتفاظ به♪
♪I hate myself for not being brave, for not trying♪
♪أكره نفسي لعدم كوني شجاعًا، لعدم محاولتي♪
♪For letting you slip away into the crowd with my own hands♪
♪لأني سمحت لك بالانزلاق إلى الحشد بيدي ♪
♪Guess we just met at the wrong time♪
♪أعتقد أننا التقينا في الوقت الخطأ♪
♪What's left of our love is nothing but ashes♪
♪ما تبقى من حبنا ليس سوى رماد♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪At the wrong time, I found the one I loved most♪
♪في الوقت الخطأ، وجدت الشخص الذي أحببته أكثر♪
♪Does that still count as luck?♪
♪هل لا يزال هذا يعتبر حظًا؟♪
♪Look at us♪
♪انظر إلينا♪
♪Like two planets that were never meant to meet♪
♪مثل كوكبين لم يكن من المفترض أن يلتقيا♪
♪Colliding across the sky♪
♪الاصطدام عبر السماء♪
♪Maybe we were never meant to be♪
♪ربما لم يكن من المفترض أن نكون معًا♪